

LEANDRO SAVAT

PRODUCT MANAGER & WEB ENGINEER

More than 15 years collaborating as: Client setter, Web Engineer with UI-UX design and Product Manager. Recently, I have specialized in leadership techniques based on psychology and behavioral patterns.

My greatest strength is my willingness and ability to learn quickly and adapt as needed, allowing me to remain agile and effective in any situation.

JOB EXPERIENCES

→ From June 2024: **Technical Product Manager** at Elixior.Digital → https://www.elixior.digital

- Led the development of Next is applications, improving team efficiency by 70% with reusable resources, agile working methodologies, and local and remote Al platforms.
- Coordinated Scrum sprints and managed the technical team to meet objectives.
- Conducted market research and reported to customers.
- Some Works:
 - https://www.amordelider.com
 - https://www.felipebeltran.com
 - https://www.lideresconproposito.com

→ From Oct 2023: Web Engineering Specialist & Functional Analytics at www.superwebpros.com

- I led web development projects using React and automations with n8n.
- I implemented automated tests with Playwright, increasing the quality of the product.
- I managed the workflow on GitHub, improving team collaboration and efficiency.

→ 2022 - 2023: Web Engineering Specialist at https://savat.ar

- I developed custom web solutions for various clients, quickly adapting to new technologies and requirements.
- I implemented improvements to existing sites, optimizing their performance and user experience.

→ 2021-2022: **Developer Analyst**.

- Performed statistical analysis and developed trend indicators in TradingView.
- Collaborated with multidisciplinary teams to improve data-driven investment strategies.

→ 2019-2021: **Community Manager**.

- Managed image production and social media management for hostels in Europe and Africa.
- Increased engagement on social media, improving visibility and bookings for the establishments.

→ From 2010: Sales, Designer and Team Leader at SAVAT Productions, Client contact,

- Direct contact with clients to analyze profiles and needs.
- Research ideas and coordinate a creative team in photography and graphic design projects.
- Implemented strategies that increase sales with neuromarketing.

→ 2008-2010: Cyber **Software Technician.**

- Managed hardware and software maintenance at an Internet café.
- Improved operational efficiency and customer satisfaction by quickly resolving technical issues.

TECHNOLOGIES

{ Excel, Notion, Photoshop, Lightroom, CaptureOne, Figma, Wordpress, Visual Studio Code, Git, Javascript, HTML, CSS, React, Next.js, Node.js, Express, JWT, Zustand, MongoDB, Postman, Strapi, Algolia, PgAdmin, Tailwind, n8n, Playwright, TypeScript, Notion, CloudFlare, Analytics... and much more }

EDUCATION

Certificates → Certificados

Languages → Spanish (Native) and English (B2)

Product Manager & Product Analytics. ProductHUB. Digital Product Management Bootcamp. University Expert in Web Engineering & Dev Bootcamps. Technological University of Mexico.

English. Step English language institute / Oral Internship on a global trip.

UTN University. Engineering student in Information Systems.



LEANDRO SAVAT

GERENTE TÉCNICO DE PRODUCTO & INGENIERIA WEB

Más de 14 años colaborando como: Client setter, Ingeniero Web con conocimientos de diseño UI-UX y Gerente de Producto Digitales. Recientemente, especializado en técnicas de liderazgo basadas en psicología y patrones de comportamiento.

Mi mayor fortaleza es mi voluntad y capacidad de aprender rápidamente y adaptarme según sea necesario, lo que me permite permanecer ágil y eficaz en cualquier situación.

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

- → Desde Junio 2024: Gerente Tecnico de Producto Digital en Elixior. Digital → https://www.elixior.digital/
 - Lideró el desarrollo de aplicaciones Next.js, mejorando la eficiencia del equipo en un 70% con recursos reutilizables, metodologías ágiles de trabajo y plataformas de IA locales y remotas.
 - Coordino sprints de Scrum y gestiono el equipo técnico para cumplir objetivos.
 - Realizó investigaciones de mercado y presentó informes a la alta dirección.

→ Desde Oct 2023: Ingeniero Web & Analista Funcional en www.superwebpros.com

- Dirigí proyectos de desarrollo web utilizando React y automatizaciones con n8n.
- Implementé pruebas automatizadas con Playwright, aumentando la calidad del producto.
- Gestioné el flujo de trabajo en GitHub, mejorando la colaboración y eficiencia del equipo.

→ 2022 - 2023: **Especialista en Ingeniería Web** Freelance.

- Desarrollé soluciones web a medida para diversos clientes, adaptándome rápidamente a nuevas tecnologías y requerimientos.
- Implementé mejoras en sitios existentes, optimizando su rendimiento y experiencia de usuario.

→ 2021-2022: Analista Desarrollador.

- Realicé análisis estadísticos y desarrollé indicadores de tendencias en TradingView.
- Colaboré con equipos multidisciplinarios para mejorar estrategias de inversión basadas en datos.

\rightarrow 2019-2021: Community Manager.

- Gestioné la producción de imágenes y el manejo de redes sociales para hostales en Europa y África.
- Aumenté el engagement en redes sociales, mejorando la visibilidad y reservas de los establecimientos.

→ From 2010: Ventas, Diseño y Lider de Equipo en SAVAT Producciones.

- Contacto directo con clientes para análisis de perfiles y necesidades.
- Investigación de ideas y coordinación de un equipo creativo en proyectos de fotografía y diseño gráfico.
- Implementé estrategias que incrementan las ventas con neuromarketing.

→ 2008-2010: Cyber **Técnico de Software.**

- Gestioné el mantenimiento de hardware y software en un cibercafé.
- Mejoré la eficiencia operativa y la satisfacción del cliente mediante la resolución rápida de problemas técnicos.

TECNOLOGÍAS

{ Excel, Notion, Photoshop, Lightroom, CaptureOne, Figma, Wordpress, Visual Studio Code, Git, Javascript, HTML, CSS, React, Next.js, Node.js, Express, JWT, Zustand, MongoDB, Postman, Strapi, Algolia, PgAdmin, Tailwind, n8n, Playwright, TypeScript, Notion, CloudFlare, Analytics... y mucho mas }

EDUCACIÓN

Carpeta de certificados → Certificados

Lenguajes → Spanish (Native) and English (B2)

Product Manager & Product Analytics. Product HUB. Digital Product Management Bootcamp.

CV in English at 1st page || CV en Español en la 2da página

Experto Universitario en **Ingeniería Web** & Bootcamps de programación. Universidad Tecnologica de Mexico TECH

English. Step English language institute / Oral Internship on a global trip. **UTN University**. Estudiante de ingeniería en sistemas en la UTN.